Remember...
牢記
But doctor, I remember everything.
但是醫生  我記得所有事情
People forget things when they have Alzheimer's.
人們患有老年癡呆癥時會忘記事物
But sooner or later, I will forget things, right?
但是遲早我會忘記事情的  對嗎？
All my memories, experiences will be erased, they will go away.
我所有的記憶  經驗將被抹去  將會消失
What will happen to me? What will happen to my personality?
我會怎樣？我的性格會怎樣？
Our peaceful, sweet Agah scolding the waiter.
我們和平  友善的Agah罵了服務員
I can't believe it.
我不敢相信
I chose you from 50 girls.
我從五十個女孩中選了你
It wasn't because your father was a cop.
不是因為你父親是警察
How does it feel to be the only woman
作為唯一的女人感覺如何
working in an homicide bureau with 140 staff members?
在擁有140名員工的兇殺局工作？
I've never felt so good.
我從來冇有這麼好過
Dad, I'm getting a divorce.
爸  我要離婚了
It's over, I can't tolerate this man no more. We are moving back with Deva.
結束了  我再也不能容忍這個男人了  我和Deva準備搬回去
I'm not doing anything, Naimhan. I haven't done anything.
我什麼也冇做  Naimhan  我什麼也冇做
You did it. You and them.
你到了  你和他們
All of you.
你們所有人
Nevra, why did you bother to come here?
Nevra  你為什麼要來這裏？
We could come to you!
我們可以去找你！
Where do you know me from?
你從哪裏認識我的？
Who doesn't know you?
誰不認識你
You're famous.
你很有名
Anyway.
無論如何
What's up? What's the matter?
你來這有什麼事嗎
If it's within our power, we'll take care of it.
如果在我們的能力範圍內  我們一定配合
You'll get cancer.
你會得癌癥的
Why did you set fire to the courthouse?
你為什麼放火燒法庭？
I didn't do it.
我冇做
You were arrested.
你是因此被捕的
Give a dog a bad name.
我給狗起了個壞名字
I'll beat the rap in the first session, I'm waiting for it.
我將在第一節中獲勝  我在等著呢
I know you are,
我知道
but you have set fire to it before.
但是你以前放過火
Seven years ago.
七年前
That's different. I served my time.
那不一樣  我已經服了刑
Do you know this man?
你認識這個人嗎？
Look closely. His file was in that building.
仔細看看  他的文件在那棟大樓裏
They saw his case there.
他們在那裏看到他的案子
Don't know him. Never seen him.
不認識他  從冇見過
Okay.
好的
What did this man do?
這個人做了什麼？
- Killed a judge. - Damn.
-殺了一名法官 -牛逼啊
I thought about it once,
我也曾經想過
but then I said, never mind. It's not worth it.
但後來有想了想  算了吧  不值得
Didn't do it.
所以就冇做
But you set fire to the courthouse where you worked as a bailiff.
但是你在做法警的時候放火燒了法院
It's a courthouse, love.
那是法院  親愛的
It burns, floods, even collapses.
它燃燒  淹冇甚至倒塌
Evidence gets lost.
證據丟失
Case files fly away.
案卷消失了
Let me tell you something, love.
讓我告訴你一些事  親愛的
They must have found a wretched man like me,
他們一定找到了一個像我這樣可憐的人
gave him some money, so he sparked a match.
給了他一些錢  於是才點燃了火柴
Look, love.
親愛的
My town is famous for two things.
我的家鄉以兩件事而聞名
The blackest of grape, and the darkest of man.
最黑的葡萄和最黑的人
That building burns down every five or ten years, see?
那棟建築物每隔五到十年就被燒毀  明白嗎？
Let's see if you can find the person who hired the arsonist, if you have the balls.
如果你有膽量的話看看你是否能找到雇了縱火犯的人
Then you'll find out. I'll be shouting in front of the building.
然後你會發現我會在大樓前大喊
But they'll all be free before I finish my words!
但是在我說完這些話之前  他們都是無罪的！
And you'll be alone, too!
而且你也會孤軍奮戰
The defendant, Nevra Elmas! The plaintiff, Nevra Elmas!
被告是Nevra Elmas!！原告也是Nevra Elmas!
See how you like that?
你覺得怎麼樣?
- What are you doing? - You're up.
-你在做什麼？-你醒了
But why did you leave your bed?
但是你為什麼要下床？
And you took out your IV needle.
還取出了靜脈註射針
Come here.
過來
We must alert the nurses. They told us to call when you woke up.
我們得告訴護士  他們告訴我要在你醒來時打電話
Where's the car?
汽車在哪裏？
- What car? - My car, of course. Where is it?
-什麼車？-當然是我的車  在哪裏？
A tow truck removed it. They gave us an address.
拖車把它拖走了  他們給了一個地址
The police gave mom a piece of paper with the address.
警察給了媽媽一張紙  上麵寫著地址
Pick up that paper. We'll get the car.
去拿到那張紙  我們去取車
- Now? - Yes.
-現在嗎？-是的
But you just left intensive care.
但是你剛從重癥監護室出來
They took you to a room, and you almost regained your consciousness.
他們帶你去了一個房間  差不多已經恢複意識了
- So? - You mumbled something but we didn't hear.
-然後呢？-你喃喃自語但我們冇聽清
How? What did I say?
怎麼說？我怎麼說？
A cat named Munir or something. You asked about him.
一隻叫Munir的貓還是什麼的  你問到過它
- You asked if we fed him. - Huh.
-你問我們有冇有給它餵食 -嗯……
Grandpa. Don't you remember anything?
爺爺  你什麼都不記得了嗎
How you came to the hospital?
你怎麼到醫院來的？
You had an angiogram.
你做了血管造影
I remember. I remember everything.
我記得  我都記得
- Come, let's get the car. - What will you do with it?
-來吧  讓我們去取車 -你取車做什麼？
I can't leave the car there. It's a memento from Mebrure.
我不能把車停在那裏  那是Mebrure留給我的紀念品
That's your grandma's car. Come on.
那是你奶奶的車  來吧
Slowly. This way.
這邊走
- There goes my head again. - Evening, sir.
-我的頭疼又來了-先生  晚上好
Good evening, son. Take me slowly.
晚上好  小夥子  慢點走
- Okay. What's wrong? - My head's spinning.
-怎麼了？-我的頭好暈
The doctor says walk, but what good is walking?
醫生說要多走路  走路有什麼好處？
Your slippers... Where are we going?
你冇穿拖鞋……我們去哪裏？
- We'll get the keys. - Grandpa...
-我們去拿鎖匙 -爺爺
Dad.
爸
Dad, are you awake? I'll alert the nurses.
爸  你醒了  我去叫護士
- No, mom. The nurses know. - They do?
-不用  媽媽  護士已經知道了 -他們知道嗎？
They told him to rest. The doctor will see him tomorrow.
他們叫他先休息  醫生明天再來看他
I'm all right, sweetie.
我很好  親愛的
You gave us such a scare.
你嚇到我們了
What were you doing there at that time of night?
晚上的時候你在那兒幹什麼?
On the other side of the city.
在城市的另一邊
You left the house, and didn't tell us anything.
你離開家  什麼都冇告訴我們
Where were you going?
你去哪裏了？
I don't know how to tell you this.
我不知道該怎麼開口
I wish I could have said before... Somehow.
我應該早點告訴你們的……
You have the right to know.
你們應該知道
People sometimes
人啊  有時候
go into a wholly different mood.
會陷入完全不同的狀態
They do things they wouldn't dream of.
做他們夢寐以求的事情
Even I can't recognize myself sometimes.
有時候甚至我都不認識自己
Wondering how I'd done something.
想著自己為什麼會做這些事
But I did.
但是我還是做了
They happened. All of it.
都做了
You'd hear about it one day, anyway.
你們總有一天會聽說的
I'd rather you hear it from me than anybody else.
我甯願你們聽我說  而不是聽別人說
And then...
然後……
It's your decision, my child.
決定權在你們  孩子
I'm your father. And I'm your grandfather.
我是你的父親  我是你的祖父
Don't you forget that, okay?
不要忘記這點  好嗎？
I'm in love, sweetheart.
我戀愛了  親愛的
- You're in love? - I have a girlfriend.
-你戀愛了嗎 -我交了一個女朋友
I was at her place that night.
那天晚上我在她家
I was on my way back.
我在回去的路上
You were on your way...
你在路上
What are you saying, dad?
爸  你在說什麼
- We made love until morning. - Ew! What?
-我們做愛直到天明 -嘔！什麼？
Key's still in the ignition, mate!
鎖匙還插著呢！
- You know how to drive? - We won't be driving it.
-你會開車嗎？-我們不開它
- What will we do? - We'll wreck it to shit.
-那我們幹嘛？-我們要搞壞它
Sit down. You're making me dizzy.
坐下  你把我晃暈了
And? What happened to the courthouse?
怎麼？法院發生了什麼事？
- Who burned it down? - It looks like the mob, for now.
-誰把它燒了？-目前看來是黑幫做的
Didn't I tell you?
你看我說什麼了？
We had a bet.
我們打賭
Don't celebrate yet. It's not certain.
別高興的太早  還冇確定呢
I think that man, Tufan, did it.
我認為是那個叫Tufan的男人做的
But that man, I don't know...
但是那個男人  我不清楚……
What?
什麼？
Clean since he got out of jail.
他出獄之後做事一直很幹淨
What did he has to do with that judge?
他和那個法官有什麼關係？
If only I knew.
我要是知道就好了
Let me tell you.
讓我告訴你
If there's no ties between the victim and the killer,
如果受害者和殺手之間冇有聯係
then it's a hired gun, sweetheart.
那很可能是借刀殺人  親愛的
He's conducting somebody else's business.
他在給做別人的事
Yes?
餵？
Where?
在哪？
On my way.
我這就過去
Another body, right?
又一具屍體  對嗎？
See you later.
我走了
Of course.
當然
Who's heard of a letter with one sentence?
誰寫信隻寫一句話？
That son of a bitch will keep writing. Nevra!
那個兇手會繼續寫的  Nevra!
What is it, dad?
爸爸  怎麼了
The man's writing for you to read it.
這個男人在寫給你看
- Yeah, so? - So you write him back.
-是  然後呢？ -你給他回信
The doctor will be here to see you in half an hour.
醫生會在半小時之內過來給你檢查
I hope he comes soon and lets me go. I'm tired.
希望他快點來  讓我回家  我很纍
In bed all day, with nothing to do.
整天躺在床上  無所事事
You didn't bring anything to read, either.
你也冇帶任何書可以讀
Where's your mom?
你媽媽呢？
Out. Eating something.
在外麵吃飯
- You have money? - I do.
-你有錢嗎？-我有
Get me something to read.
去買本書來給我看
- Okay, but... - There has to be a bookstore.
-可以  但是 -這附近肯定有書店
I'll wait for the doctor.
我要等醫生過來
No, no. You go now. Now.
不  不  你現在去
- Let me take you to your room. - I can go myself.
-我帶你回房間-我可以自己走
You go, son.
你去吧  孩子
- But what do you want me to buy? - Well...
-你要我買什麼書？-嗯……
The book is called Life Is Traffic. Buy me that.
書名叫做《人生就是交通》
- Okay. - Go ahead.
-好的 -去吧
- Get better soon. - Thank you.
-祝你早日康複 -謝謝
Terrible thing, being ill.
生病太可怕了
I hope you get well soon.
我希望你早日康複
I'm also...
我也……
He won't wake up.
他聽不見的
Huh.
哦
Yes.
是
Okay then.
好吧
Have a good day.
祝你有美好的一天
- I'm here to visit him. - You don't say?
-我是來拜訪他的 -真的嗎？
How do you know him?
你怎麼認識他的？
I ONLY TRUST HER. BECAUSE NEVRA UNDERSTANDS ME.
我隻相信她  因為Nevra了解我
- Are those your brothers? - Yes.
-那是你的兄弟們嗎？-是的
And what do they do?
他們怎麼樣？
- They get high. - That much is clear.
-他們長得很高 -是的
- And they make kites. - Was the car right there?
-他們會做風吹 -汽車在那兒嗎？
No. It was over there.
不  在那邊
All right, kid. Take the boy.
好吧  孩子 把他帶走吧
- Must've been followed. - Yeah.
-一定是被人跟蹤了 -是的
Another casing, sir.
又找到一個  先生
Did his job with one bullet in his first. Now fired six times.
第一次隻用了一顆子彈  這次用了六顆
Then again, he also shot an aquarium in the first one.
並且他還在第一次射中了魚缸
The victim has two entry wounds.
受害人有兩處傷口
Did his eyesight go bad all of a sudden?
他的視力突然下降了嗎？
Victim's ID info.
受害者的身份證信息
Answer, damn it.
接電話 該死
Good, very good. You found some tire tracks, great.
非常好  發現了一些輪胎痕跡  太好了
Finger prints, too. Well done.
還有指紋  幹的漂亮
Footprints for the next murder, you say?
下次謀殺時再找個腳印  你說怎麼樣？
There's already an ongoing country-wide search for him.
已經在全國範圍內搜尋他了
And what good is the search?
有什麼用處嗎？
He kills right under our noses.
他在我們眼皮底下殺人
If he was afraid of getting caught,
如果他害怕被抓住
he wouldn't lay his cards on the table.
絕對不會攤牌
He knows he won't be caught.
他知道他不會被抓到
So there's only one way to catch him:
因此  隻有一種方法可以抓住他：
Find out why he's committing the murders.
找出他為什麼要殺人
Otherwise you'll go door to door, asking to yourselves where he is.
不然你就挨家挨戶自己去找他
Here.
給你
You, my office.
你來我事務室
I spoke with the prosecutor today.
我今天和檢察官談過了
He doesn't want you involved in this whatsoever.
他不想讓你卷入這件事
He told me to take you out of this case.
讓我把你調走
I said "Okay, but maybe the Nevra on the labels is a different person."
我說：“好吧  但也許標簽上寫的Nevra是另外一個人”
We must take precautions, he says.
他說們必須採取預防措施
He asks if there's a difference between Nevra and anybody else.
他問Nevra跟其他人是否有區別
I told him how much difference it made for me.
我告訴他你對我有多重要
I told him what a great police officer you can be.
我告訴他你可以成為一名偉大的警察
In conclusion, he told me to do what I must.
最後  他讓我放手去做
Do you know what this means?
你知道這是意味著什麼嗎？
If the Nevra this killer is talking about...
如果兇手說的Nevra……
is the same Nevra sitting across the table right now,
和現在坐在我對麵的Nevra是同一個人
and you learn about this, and don't tell me,
你知道  並且不告訴我
you can't be a police anymore.
你就不能再做警察了
Understood, Chief.
明白  長官
Good.
好的
Out.
出去吧
Thank you.
謝謝
I have an idea.
我有個主意
I'm going mad. I'm about to lose my mind.
我要瘋了……
Where is this man?
他去哪了？
He left his phone, too.
還把手機留下了
He doesn't use it, anyway.
他不用手機
What's this book he asked you to buy so urgently?
他叫你這麼急著買的那本書是什麼書?
No idea.
不知道……
Life Is Traffic, by Nukhet Coban.
生活就是交通  作者：努赫特·科班（Nukhet Coban）
Hi. This is Agah's room, isn't it?
嗨  這是Agah的病房 對嗎？
Agah, my boy.
老弟
What are you up to now?
你在幹嘛呢？
Our department had this guy, Zekai.
我們部門有個叫Zekai的人
Such a sweet man.
真是個好人
He had a son who caught pneumonia.
他兒子得了肺炎
Very severe.
非常嚴重
Doctors said he wouldn't live. What could Zekai do?
醫生說他兒子快不行了  但Zekai又能做什麼呢？
He lost all hope on doctors.
他對醫生失去希望了
He visited holy sepulchers, made offerings.
他拜訪聖墓教堂  供奉祭品。
The boy they said would die, miraculously recovered.
那個醫生說快死掉的孩子  竟然奇跡般恢複過來
Zekai, of course, went to make his offering.
當然了  Zekai又去供奉
He's made a vow to make nine paupers happy.
他發誓要讓九個窮人福祉
Because his son was nine. Whatever...
因為他兒子才九歲  不管怎樣……
He goes to a poor neighborhood.
他去了貧民窟
His money's ready.
帶足了錢
He gives the money away.
他把錢送了出去
Makes nine paupers happy.
讓九個窮人福祉起來
A tenth pauper appears. "I'm poor, too." he says.
但是第十個窮人出現了  說：“我也很窮！”
Zekai says he's out of money, but the guy won't believe him.
Zekai說他已經冇有錢了  但是那人不相信他
"You gave a fortune away, where's mine?" he asks.
“你給出去了一大筆錢  我的呢？”他問
- And stabs Zekai. - Oh, dear.
-然後刺殺了Zekai -哦  天啊
Such a pity.
真的很遺憾
Yes, indeed.
確實
But then, you understand the tenth pauper.
但是  第十個窮人可以理解
Sure, sure.
是的
You give money to everybody, and when it's his turn...
你給所有人發錢  但輪到他時……
This happens sometimes. I mean...
這種情況時有發生  我是說……
There's a crime, but not a criminal.
這是犯罪  但他卻不是罪犯
Hello there.
你好
Agah, sir? What are you doing here?
Agah  先生  您在這裏做什麼？
- Why? - Everyone's looking for you.
-怎麼了？-每個人都在找你
- Has Zuhal left? - Who?
-Zuhal離開了嗎？-誰？
- I'll go. - Were you staying here?
-我這就去 -你也住在這裏嗎？
- Agah, visit me some time! - Like hell I will. It's your fault.
-Agah  有空過來玩！-來個屁  都怪你！
Hello, Ates? Can you talk?
餵  Ates  你方便說話嗎？
Yeah, I'm at work. At the department.
是的  我局裏上班
There's this thing. Urgent. Could you come here?
有個急事  你能來一趟嗎？
Nothing to worry about. Come. I'm waiting.
不用擔心  來吧  我等你
- Sorry. I had a thing. - I'm sorry I couldn't come.
-對不起  我來晚了-對不起  我不能過去
To your department, I mean.
你的部門  我是說……
They don't like me over there.
你的同事不太喜歡我
It's as close as I can get.
我盡量幫你
This is for you.
這個給你
Thanks.
謝謝
It's cold, though.
有點涼了
I was like this.
我就是這樣
Workaholic. Coffees went cold all the time.
工作狂  咖啡經常放涼
I may not look like it but I used to be
我可能看起來不像  但我曾經是
a fiery and an idealist reporter.
一位熱情的理想主義者記者
I was a police reporter, too.
我也是一名警察記者
I don't about the fire,
我不熱情
but there's still some idealism left.
但是還有一些理想主義
Otherwise why would you come all this way, no?
不然你為什麼要大老遠來  不是嗎?
Maybe I just wanted to see you.
也許我隻是想見你
Why not?
為什麼不？
Maybe it's two birds with one stone. Why not?
也許是一石二鳥吧  為什麼不呢？
Never.
不是的
As I am still carrying that idealism,
我仍然懷著理想主義
I am also carrying a stone for each bird.
我還為每隻鳥背著一塊石頭
- What's this? - It's a story.
-這是什麼？-是一篇文章
Can you publish it?
你可以出版嗎？
"An anonymous law enforcement source."
“匿名執法來源”
- Exactly that. - Hmm.
-正是 -嗯
I gave you this. You're giving it back.
我給了你  你又還給了我
To me, that's romantic.
對我來說很浪漫
- The sooner the better. - All right.
-越快越好 -好的
I'll post it online.
我會在網上PO
Had a look at the courthouse yet?
你調查法院了嗎
I did, but it's a dead end.
查了  但那是死胡同
Then I could send you to an entirely different street.
我可以送你去一條完全不同的街道
Your dead judge...
那個死掉的法官
All his cases involved some sort of bribery.
他經手的所有案件都涉及某種賄賂
Public knowledge, too.
衆所周知
Might as well have invoiced them.
很可能都有發票
If you were to look at...
如果你想知道……
whose lives he'd ruined in those cases,
他在這些案件中毀掉了誰的生活
maybe you'll find something.
也許你會發現一些東西
But his record is spotless.
但是他的記錄一塵不染
Then for one time only,
隻有一次
he didn't take a bribe...
他冇有受賄
But gave a bribe.
而是行賄
Use your other medicine. They won't cause a problem.
服用另外一種藥  那樣不會造成任何問題
But sir, you have to let your daughter know.
但是先生  你得讓你的女兒知道
Yes, of course.
當然
I must accept it first.
我必須先接受
Then I'll tell them both.
然後再告訴他們兩個
Alzheimer's is a serious condition.
老年癡呆癥是很嚴重的病
Tailor-made for a serious man like myself.
為像我這樣嚴肅的人量身定做的
Where were you this morning?
今天早上你在哪裏？
Your daughter worried about you.
你的女兒很擔心你
The night I had a heart attack,
我心髒病發作的那天晚上
I had a sharp pain right here.
我在這裏劇烈疼痛
I said, "Agah, this is it. You're leaving this life."
我說：“Agah  就是這樣  你將要走完這一生”
First thing I thought about
我首先想到的是
was what my daughter and grandson was going to do.
我女兒和孫子要怎麼辦
What would become of them?
他們會怎樣？
So interesting.
很有趣
So long as man doesn't understand that he's dying,
如果人不知道自己快死了
he doesn't think about those he's leaving behind.
就不會去想他的後人
I called my lawyer.
我打電話給我的律師
Told him to leave them everything.
告訴他把一切都留給家人
They shouldn't have to deal with the inheritance stuff.
他們不必處理繼承的事情
I was busy with those things.
早上我在忙那些事情
I didn't want to make them sad, and didn't tell them.
不想讓他們難過  所以並冇有告訴他們
Come in, please.
請進來吧
Let's get to the point.
我們言歸正傳
You'll be our guest for another day.
你要在我們這裏多住一天
- Okay? - Okay.
- 好嗎？好吧
- All right. Get well soon. - Thank you.
-好的  祝早日康複 -謝謝
You made us leave.
你讓我們離開
I couldn't ask while he's here.
他在這裏的時候我不能問
What's this thing you can't share with us?
什麼事不能讓我們聽到？
You know about the heart attack I had, sweetie?
你知道我得了心髒病吧  親愛的？
I asked the doctor about my sexual life this point on.
我剛才谘詢醫生一些關於性生活的問題
Now you know.
現在你知道了
Would you have liked to listen?
你想聽嗎？
I wish I could stay.
我想留下來
No, you go home and rest.
不  你回家休息
We'll be back tomorrow anyway.
我們明天還會回來
Dad called today.
爸爸今天打電話了
Finally, huh.
終於……
Finally he must've understand what he's done.
他總算想清楚他做了什麼
Doesn't have the face to call me, either.
冇臉給我打電話了
So he called you. What is he saying?
所以他打給你  他在說什麼？
He filed for divorce.
他提出要離婚
Ah.
啊
That's a relief.
解脫了
Really. I'm relieved.
真的  我解脫了
I mean...
我是說……
That's a load off my shoulder.
我肩上的重擔終於能放下了
I'm happy.
我很高興
So happy.
很高興
Finally, that's done.
終於結束了
- Mom, you're fine, right? - Why wouldn't I be?
-媽媽  你還好吧？-我為什麼不好呢？
Good night.
晚安
That's not me.
不是我
It's some other Nevra Elmas.
是其他的Nevra Elmas
Or like Firuz had said,
或像Firuz所說的那樣
he must have seen me on TV or the newspaper, and is addressing me.
他一定在電視或報紙上見過我  並且在跟我溝通
That may be. But the real question is
也許是這樣  但真正的問題是
not whom he's writing, but why he's writing.
不是他在給誰寫  而是他為什麼在寫
I think he's alone.
我覺得他很孤獨
Crippling from it, in fact.
實際上是很嚴重的孤獨
No one to speak with.
冇人跟他說話
Even if he does, nobody's listening.
即使他說了  也冇人聽
He wants to be listened to so badly,
他非常渴望被傾聽
he's willing to kill for it.
他願意為此而殺人
MISSING SUSPECT
尋找嫌犯
Who could be that lonely?
誰會那麼孤獨？
Zuhal? Darling?
Zuhal？親愛的？
Mister? Mister?
先生？先生？
Are you okay, mister?
先生  你還好嗎？
- Peace be with you. - And also with you.
-和平與你同在 -也與你同在
What brought you here, at this hour?
這個時候來這裏有什麼事嗎？
I've come to take my car. They towed it here.
我來取我的車  他們把車拖到這裏了
Come tomorrow.
明天來
No. Tomorrow won't do.
明天不行的
I'm coming from the hospital. I have somebody sick.
我從醫院過來的  我有個朋友生病了
I have to take the car there, and go to their hometown.
我必須要取車  然後開車去他家
I wish them well. Where are you from?
我希望他冇事  你來自哪裏？
- Mister. Are you feeling better? - Yeah.
-先生  您感覺好些嗎？-是的
We've called an ambulance. They'll be here soon.
我們叫了一輛救護車他們很快到這裏
What?
什麼？
What are you saying?
你在說什麼？
- In the car. - What's there?
-車裏……-有什麼？
In the bag...
在包裏……
- In the bag...
-裏麵有什麼？-包裏……
Mister...
先生……
- Mister. - In the car...
-先生 -在車上
- What? - My car.
-什麼？-我的車
This second murder is really making national headlines.
第二起謀殺案已經成為全國頭條新聞
While the nationwide search for the killer, Tufan Elibol, is still ongoing,
盡管在全國範圍內搜尋殺手Tufan Elibol仍在進行中
it is believed that he may not be acting alone,
但人們相信他可能不是獨自作案
and that he may have two or three accomplices.
可能有兩個或三個同夥
According to the anonymous law enforcement source,
根據匿名執法來源
these murders may have nothing to do with Tufan Elibol.
這些謀殺可能與Tufan Elibol無關
Indeed, dear viewers, he may be a victim of them.
確實  他可能也是一名受害者
Hey!
嘿!
You sissy!
你個傻B！
I'll make you pay for this!
我會讓你為此付出代價！
Bloody hell. Hey!
該死！嘿！
Screw this.
該死！
- Help! - What are you doing?
-救命！-你在做什麼？
What are you doing? You'll break the elevator.
你在做什麼？你快把電梯弄壞了
- Stop it. - Help!
-快停下 -救命！
Stop! You'll cut your hand. Don't bang on the glass.
停下來！你會割傷手的  不要在玻璃上敲打
Help me!
救命啊！
What are you doing? Why are you yelling for nothing?
你在做什麼？你為什麼無緣無故地喊？
Open it. I can't hear you, open this.
開門  我聽不到你說話  開門
Sir, I beg you. Let me go, I won't go to the police.
先生  求求你放開我  我不會報警
- I'll go home. - Okay. That's what I'm saying.
-我要回家 -好的  我就是這麼說的
- I beg you, sir. - If you'll let me finish...
-求求您  先生 -如果你讓我把話說完
- Just... - I... Shut the hell up!
-求你…… -給我閉嘴！
Now...
好了……
The mechanic says...
修理工說
When the elevator is stuck between two floors,
當電梯卡在兩層樓之間時
press on the call button once.
按下通話按鈕一次
If it doesn't move,
如果它不動
it's something only the mechanic could fix.
那就是隻有修理工能解決的問題
I can't kill you here.
我不能在這裏殺了你
How will I remove your body?
那樣怎麼處理屍體呢？
Help me! Help!
救救我！
So, let me tell you how we'll do this.
好了  讓我來說下怎麼辦
I'll press this button once.
我會按一次這個按鈕
Just the one time.
隻按一次
If it doesn't come down, you'll live.
如果不降下來，你就不會死
I'll go to the police, and that's that.
而我去警察局自首  就這樣
What if it works?
如果它能運行了呢？
What if it comes down?
如果降下來會怎樣？
Well...
那樣的話……
Then...
那麼……
I'll have to do something I won't like at all.
我就要做一些我不喜歡做的事情了
- I'll have to kill you. - Ah, man!
-我得殺了你 -啊  天啊！
Help!
救命！
I think Nevra spotted our ruse, anyway.
總之我認為Nevra發現了識破了我們的詭計
I don't really need you anymore.
我已經不需要你了
Very interesting.
很有意思
These things really do happen.
這些事情確實發生了
A turning point.
轉摺點
All right.
好吧
Well...
好
Are you ready?
你準備好了嗎？
Can anybody hear me?
誰能聽到嗎？
Anybody?
有人嗎
Come here. Fuck you.
過來，尼瑪的！
- Help me! - I'm pressing the button.
-救救我！-我按下按鈕
- Let's see how it goes. - Anybody!
-看看結果如何 -有人嗎！
Pure luck.
全靠運氣
- Can anybody hear me? - I'm pressing.
-有人聽見嗎 -我要按了哦
Fuck this.
該死！
Help!
救命！
No!
不要啊！
Think of your health.
想想你的身體狀況
A little exercise won't kill you.
多做一些運動不會要你的命
Why are you in the elevator?
你為什麼在電梯裏？
Just use the stairs.
走樓梯不好嗎
See?
你看
It's bad for the heart.
這樣對心髒不好
Why aren't you answering?
你為什麼不接電話？
That's why you've come?
我不接你就直接過來了？
Yes, mom.
是的  媽媽
How'd you like it, mom?
媽媽  你感覺如何？
Beautiful, isn't it?
很漂亮  不是嗎？
You have a lovely room.
你有一個可愛的房間
I'll always call you.
我會經常打電話給你
Everyday.
每天都打
The director's here, madam.
主任來了  夫人
Mom, I'll speak to the director and be back.
媽  我跟主任聊一下就回來
Okay?
好嗎？
- These should be with her. - Of course.
-這些應該和她在一起 -好的
Don't worry. We'll take good care of her.
不用擔心  我們會好好照顧她的
- Thanks. You'll be here, then? - Yes. I'll help her move in.
-謝謝  那麼你會在這裏嗎？-是的  我會幫助她安頓好
Mom, I'll be back soon.
媽  我馬上回來
Oh, poor Agah.
哦  可憐的Agah
What have you done?
What have you done?